jobseeq.com 2019-03-09

# JobSeeq | Privacy Policy

Updated November 10, 2018

Welcome to JobSeeq.com ("JobSeeq"). We respect the privacy of our users who access and/or use JobSeeq and are committed to protecting the personally identifiable information we collect about you.

By using the JobSeeq website, or submitting your information to us by any other means, you are subjecting your information to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact JobSeeq at 1171 E Alosta Ave #10008, Azusa, CA 91702 or via our contact form located here.

## What This Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers how JobSeeq's collects, uses, and shares your personal information when you visit JobSeeq's website and when you use JobSeeq's services.

JobSeeq is not responsible for any practices of third parties that we do not own or control. This includes the collection of your information from websites that we may link to. Please review the privacy policies of those sites so that you may better understand how they collect, use, and share your information.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

JobSeeq may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any updates on our website located at www.JobSeeq.com.

JobSeeq encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this site and/or submitting your personally identifiable information to JobSeeq will be subject to the then current Privacy Policy.

## Information That We Collect

JobSeeq collects two types of information about you when you use our website and our services. The first type of personal information we collect is anything you actively choose to disclose to JobSeeq ("Active Information"). The second type of information is anonymous aggregate information collected in a way that is not visible to you or others visiting the site ("Passive Information").

## Active Information

JobSeeq may collect or receive Active Information about you when you submit your personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, your username, password, first and last name, email address, street address, gender, occupation, interests, job search history, and any other data included in any submitted profile or search. JobSeeq also collects information on the pages you access through our site and any other information you may volunteer, such as survey information, ratings, reviews, questions, and answers.

## Passive Information

JobSeeq may also collect your Passive Information by recording actions taken by you on our site including, but not limited to, clicks, page views, IP address, and search queries. We may store this information in our equipment or the equipment of third party technology providers. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you.

## How We Use Your Information

JobSeeq will only use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

For the purpose of identifying users and delivering relevant content and advertisements, our partner LiveRamp may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser or a unique ID for your mobile device. To opt-out of LiveRamp cookies, please go [here](http://liveramp.com/opt_out/).

## Email Communications

JobSeeq respects your email preferences and will never provide your email address to a third party without your permission, except as may be prescribed elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. If you provide us your email address, JobSeeq may email you job alerts, account notifications, news, offers, surveys, promotions, and other communications. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. JobSeeq may use demographic and/or profile data, including but not limited to search history, to tailor your experience on JobSeeq's site, show you content that JobSeeq thinks you may be interested in, and display content according to your preferences. JobSeeq, or companies we partner with, may contact you based on your interests such as job postings and career development opportunities. 

If you do not want to receive particular types of email messages from JobSeeq, follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email message to notify us of your preferences, or click here.

## Administer Site

We may use other companies as necessary to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Every effort will be made to safeguard your privacy when it may be accessed by other companies, including but not limited to technology providers; however, JobSeeq will not be liable for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies.

JobSeeq may use your IP address to administer our site. Your IP address may also be used to help identify you, your location, and to gather broad demographic information. Nothing shall restrict JobSeeq from maintaining your data following your termination of your use of JobSeeq's site. JobSeeq may delete your user data at JobSeeq's sole discretion.

## Children's Privacy

JobSeeq's site is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. JobSeeq is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities. JobSeeq does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor does JobSeeq target its services or site to children under the age of 13. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 17 ask and receive permission from their parent or guardian prior to using JobSeeq or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

## Protect Yourself

JobSeeq uses automated processes and third party aggregators to collect and present information that has been created by third parties, so we cannot verify the accuracy or legitimacy of all job postings displayed on our site. We strongly encourage you to exercise caution when providing information about yourself to others online, including when you apply for jobs found on JobSeeq.

Never provide your social security number, credit card information, bank account details, or unnecessary personal information to a potential employer. Never participate in a financial transaction of any sort with a potential employer. Always be cautious of opportunities that sound too good to be true or require you to act as a financial intermediary, particularly for an overseas person.

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Jobseeq may use cookies to keep track of your session and advertising delivery. Jobseeq or our partners may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save a password associated with a user profile. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use third-party cookies to record information (excluding your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites and directly in emails/communications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you on others websites. Our partners may also link the nonpersonal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, hashed version of your email address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. You can learn more [here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You can opt-out of this type of advertising [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

## Links to Third Party Sites

JobSeeq may provide links to external websites. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by JobSeeq of those external websites. You acknowledge that JobSeeq is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that JobSeeq is not responsible for the content of such external websites. Your use of external websites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the external websites. 

## Assignment

If there is a change of control in JobSeeq's business (whether by merger, sale, or otherwise) or if there is an asset sale, the user information, including personal information, could be sold as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information potentially could be used by the purchaser. However, if that business materially changes this statement or the information handling practices as described in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified by email and/or through a notice posted on the site, and you may opt-out of the use of your existing information in a new manner. This Privacy Policy inures to the benefit of any successors or assigns of JobSeeq or the assets of JobSeeq.

## Ad Preferences

If you would like to read more about your ad preferences, please [click here](http://dyn.adki.com/preferences.php?p=5060&e=&r=0).

## Conditions of Use

If you decide to use JobSeeq's site or services, your use and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy.

## Contact Information

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
